lightonline.com.au 2018-04-08

# Privacy Policy

**Australian Privacy Act 1988**

LightOnline is a retailer, which trades utilising the web through its websites and in stores around Australia.

Further Information about us can be obtained by contacting us during normal business hours on:  
 **Phone:**  03  9819 1777 or by  
 **Fax:**  03 9819 1851 or by  
 **E-mail** : [webmaster@lightonline.com.au](mailto:webmaster@lightonline.com.au)

LightOnline acknowledges and is committed to protecting your privacy. We will collect, use and disclose and hold personal information in accordance with the Privacy Act 1998 ("the Act"). We will let you know:

o    When we collect information about you; and

o    What information we collect and hold about you and why we collect such information; and

o    How that information is used by us and the organizations, or types of organizations that the information would usually be disclosed to; and

o    If the law requires the collection of such information; and

o    The consequences, if any, of you not disclosing such information; and

o    That you can access such information and how you can access such information; and

o    How you can correct such information if it is not correct.

 **Collection of personal information**  
LightOnline does not collect personal information unless it is necessary for us to carry out our functions and activities as a retailer. We only collect such information by lawful and fair means and in an unobtrusive way. You may provide us with personal information about yourself or others each time you contact us by phone, fax, letter or email. We need to use this information to provide you with our services and/or products. This information will be used and managed as follows:

 **Disclosure of personal information and marketing**  
We will use and disclose your personal information for the primary purposes of our business as a retailer or a purpose related to our primary purpose such as marketing, where you consent to such disclosure or such disclosure is permitted by the Act. In addition we use such information to market to you products and services offered by LightOnline unless you have indicated that you do not wish to obtain such marketing offers or material. Such a request can be made to us. We will in such circumstances only use the personal information provided for the sole purpose of providing the service you have requested.

LightOnline may utilise the services of contractors from time to time for the purposes of marketing and undertaking services as promoted by LightOnline. Your personal information will be provided to these businesses for the purposes of ensuring that our services are marketed to you or to enable a service to be provided to you.

We will not otherwise provide your personal information to a third party without your approval.

 **Security and access of personal information**  
The personal information you have provided to us will be kept confidential and secure and will not be accessible for unauthorised use, amendment or disclosure. Only LightOnline staff that have been trained on our privacy policy will have access to such information. You are able to access the personal information we hold about you at any time by contacting our Privacy Officer by phone, fax or e-mail.

 **Ensuring accuracy of the personal information we hold**  
We will reasonably attempt to ensure that the personal information we hold about you is accurate, up to date and complete. To assist us to do this please provide us with the correct information and inform us if your details have changed. This can be done by providing us with details of any changes to your information by fax or e-mail. If we deny you access or deny a request for correction we will provide you with reasons why we have denied you access or corrected such information in the circumstances.

 **LightOnline Privacy Policy**  
Due to the importance of your privacy, our privacy policy will be reviewed and monitored regularly. A copy is available by contacting us.

 **LightOnline Privacy Complaint Process**  
If you are concerned with the way LightOnline has handled your personal information, please contact us with your complaint. We will make available to you a privacy complaint form, which you will be required to complete and return to us. This will ensure the prompt investigation of your complaint. If we have not handled your personal information in an appropriate way we will take steps to remedy your concerns promptly.
